saveya.com 2016-11-02

# Privacy Policy - SaveYa

PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY BEFORE USING THE SAVEYA MOBILE APPLICATION AND/OR ITS AFFILIATED SITE, SAVEYA.COM (COLLECTIVELY THE "SAVEYA PLATFORM"). BY VISITING OR USING THE SAVEYA PLATFORM, YOU AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT SUCH AGREEMENT CONSTITUTES A BINDING CONTRACT BETWEEN YOU AND SAVEYA, LLC AND ITS AFFILIATED ENTITIES (COLLECTIVELY THE "COMPANY"). IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY, PLEASE DO NOT USE THE SAVEYA PLATFORM. 

**_Collection of Information_**

We collect nonpublic personal and financial information ("Personal Information") from you and other users of the SaveYa Platform. For example: 

  * In order to use this SaveYa Platform, you must first register by creating a password-protected SaveYa account ("Account"). During registration you are required to provide Personal Information, including but not limited to your name, telephone number, email address, and street address.
  * Prior to your first purchase on the SaveYa Platform, you are required to provide payment information in order for you to pay us.
  * Prior to your first sale on the SaveYa Platform, you are required to provide payment information in order for us to pay you. As a seller, you also may be required to provide us your date of birth as well as you social security number, EIN, or TIN.
  * We collect additional information about your purchases and how you interact with the SaveYa Platform, including through the use of log/session files and cookies (discussed further below).
  * We use Google Analytics, and you can visit http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/ to learn how Google Analytics collects and processes data. We also use specific Google Analytics Advertiser Features (Google Display Network Impression Reporting, Remarketing with Google Analytics, and Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting). You can visit https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/ to learn how to opt out of these Google Analytics Advertising Features.

 ** _Use of Information_**

We use this Personal Information to enable you to use the SaveYa Platform, to guard against fraud, and to operate the SaveYa Platform and related services. If you purchase or sell a product or service from us, we use certain Personal Information you have provided to the Company for billing purposes and to fill your orders or process sales of gift cards to us. If we have trouble processing an order or acquisition, we will use this information to contact you. We may use location-based notifications to provide offers to you on your mobile device. If you don’t wish to receive these offer notifications, you can turn off this functionality in your mobile device settings. 

We also may share or disclose Personal Information to third parties as follows: 

  * As necessary to effect, administer, or enforce a transaction requested or authorized by you, in connection with servicing or processing a product or service you requested or authorized, or in connection with maintaining or servicing your Account.
  * To protect against or address potential or actual fraud, identity theft, unauthorized transactions, claims, or other liability
  * In response to a specific request from law enforcement officials
  * To comply with a judicial proceeding, a court order, or legal process served on us
  * As required by law
  * To consumer reporting agencies
  * To resolve customer disputes
  * For institutional risk control
  * When we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights
  * To vendors providing Company business or professional services, including to quantify converted sales with or from our affiliate partners
  * In connection with a proposed or actual sale , merger, transfer, or exchange of all or a portion of the Company

 ** _Verification and Supplementation of Information_**

In order to guard against fraud, we may on occasion verify and/or supplement the Personal Information you submitted to us with information from third party sources. 

**_Updates and Newsletter_**

We will occasionally send you information regarding the SaveYa Platform and related Company products and services regarding marketing offers for our products and announcements regarding SaveYa Platform updates and operations. When you are making a purchase through the SaveYa Platform, at check-out you will be able to opt in to receiving the SaveYa newsletter. You can stop receiving these newsletters by deselecting this option in your Account or by choosing not to opt in the next time you are checking out. 

**_Service-related Announcements_**

We will send you strictly service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option of deactivating your Account by calling 800-543-7927. 

**_Customer Service_**

Based upon the Personal Information you provide us, we will send you a welcome email. We will also communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to provide the services you request, and to manage your Account. 

**_Information Sharing and Disclosure_**

The Company is the sole owner of the information collected on the SaveYa Platform. We do not share any of your Personal Information with any third party except as set forth above in the "Use of Information" section. 

**_Legal Disclaimer_**

We reserve the right to disclose your Personal Information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, a court order, or legal process served on us. We also may use your Personal Information as set forth above in the "Use of Information" section. 

**_Log/Session Files and Cookies_**

As is true of most websites and mobile apps, we gather certain information automatically and store it in session/log files and cookies (small text files that are stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes). Some of our partners use cookies on our SaveYa Platform and web beacons; we have no access to or control over these cookies and web beacons. 

This information stored in session/log files and cookies includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, device tokens, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. We may tie this information to your Personal Information in order to guard against fraud, analyze trends (e.g., regarding usage and sales), and administer and optimize the SaveYa Platform. We also may use collected information as set forth above in the "Use of Information" section. 

**_Updating Personal Information_**

If your Personal Information changes, you may correct or update it by signing into your SaveYa Account. If you no longer desire to use the SaveYa Platform, you may deactivate your Account by calling our customer support at 800-543-7927. 

**_Security_**

The security of your Personal Information is important to us. We have implemented security safeguards designed to protect the Personal Information that you provide in accordance with industry standards. Access to your data is password-protected, and sensitive data (such as credit card information) is protected by SSL encryption when it is exchanged between your web browser and our services. To protect any data you store on our servers, we also regularly monitor our system for possible vulnerabilities and attacks, and we use a secure enterprise data center. However, since the Internet is not a 100% secure environment, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information that you transmit to us. There is no guarantee that information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards. You acknowledge that you provide your Personal Information at your own risk and the Company shall not be liable for the unauthorized access of your Personal Information. It is also your responsibility to protect the security of your login information. Please note that emails, instant messaging, and similar means of communication are not encrypted, and we strongly advise you not to communicate any confidential information through these means. Please help keep your Account safe by using a strong password. 

We retain Personal Information you provide while your Account is in existence or as needed to provide you services. We may retain your Personal Information even after you have closed your Account if retention is reasonably necessary to comply with our legal obligations, meet regulatory requirements, prevent fraud and abuse, or enforce this privacy policy. We may also retain Personal Information if requested by law enforcement, or to provide support-related reporting and trend analysis ( _e.g._ , of purchases). 

When it is appropriate to destroy or delete information, we will remove the information from our primary/online systems. There may be secondary/offline sources containing Personal Information at the Company, including backups and paper copies. As appropriate, we will take reasonable steps to remove such information from those sources as well. 

**_Business Transitions_**

In the event the Company goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your Personal Information will likely be among the assets transferred. We will send you a notification via email or by an alert in your Account if there are any such changes in ownership or control of your Personal Information. 

**_Changes in this Privacy Policy_**

We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. We will send you a notification via email or by an alert in your Account if we make material changes to this privacy policy. 

**_Questions about this Privacy Policy_**

If you have questions about this privacy policy, you can contact us by calling 800-543-7927 or emailing legal@saveya.com. 

**_Effective Date_**

This privacy policy is effective as of March 2015.
